MOHAMAD RIVALDO DWIPUTRA NAMARE

Cinere, Depok | 08118258488

rivaldonamare8@gmail.com | rivaldonamare.github.io/rivaldonamare/

SUMMARY

Final-year student of Informatic Engineering at Gunadarma University. Interest in Web-Based Application, Mobile Development, Graphics Design and SEO. I am fast learning about new things. I want to improve my knowledge and skills and gain more experience to become great programmer.

EDUCATION

Gunadarma University

Undergraduate | Informatic Engineering

2018 – present

GPA: 3.29

SMKN 29 Jakarta

Graduate | Electrical Avionics

2015 - 2018

EXPERIENCE

Advanced Accounting A Laboratory - Gunadarma University

Programmer

2020 – present

- Providing technical & material projects to support the lab (Database concepts, SQL, Visual Basic)
- Troubleshooting software & computer hardware

Politeknik Tempo

Programmer Internship

Developed Politeknik Tempo website

Nov 2021- Nov 2022

- Assist in the addition of new content to the Politeknik Tempo website
- Build a new website for Politeknik Tempo Major

Kementrian Pendidikan, Kebudayaan, Riset, dan Teknologi

Staff Internship

Jul 2021 -Aug 2021

- Guide and handled more than 300 candidates and 10 examiners
- Help candidats and examiners if they have problem
- Monitor candidates and examiner

COURSES

• Java Programming Language Fundamentals 2018

Fundamental Web Programing 2018

Fundamental DBMS (Database Management Sistem) 2019

• Mastering Laravel 2021

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- Java
- MySQL
- Flutter
- Laravel
- CodeIgniter

- Time Management
- Team Work
- Hardworking
- Fast learner
- Comunicative

- English
- Bahasa Indonesia